Aren't you, um...
a bit close, Petra?
Well, she had you all to herself earlier.
It wasn't fair!
You don't mind, right?
Um... It's not like that, Petra-chan.
Subaru and I were just...
Right! We had important things to talk about!
I'm not gonna lose to you! You hear me?!
Emilia-tan, she's only a kid.
You just have to smile and
laugh off what kids say.
No way.
Even if she's a child,
I can't take such a lackadaisical attitude.
Lackadaisical? Who says
that in this day and age?
You're teasing me again!
I'm not a kid!
Okay, sorry.
I need to thank you, Petra.
You kept your promise to not
leave Emilia-tan alone.
There are so many people I need
to thank when things calm down.
I'm really grateful to Crusch-san and her gang,
and Anastasia-san and her
people helped a lot, too.
And I hate to admit it,
but the same goes for Julius and those guys.
I'm even indebted to Otto.
Did you say something, Natsuki-san?
Nah, nothing.
Just that I'm super grateful to you, too!
Gosh, what brought that on?
You're making me blush.
And...
What's wrong, Subaru?
Oh, um, just...
Emilia-tan...
There's something really
important I need to tell you.
Okay. What is it?
This is really hard for me to
say, but please hear me out.
Oh, and of course, I'm prepared to be
knocked out by Ram when I tell her!
But I want you to hear it first.
Okay.
It's actually... about Rem.
Rem said that she, um...
You'll still keep me by your side from now on?
Y-You see what I'm getting at, right?
I mean, well... Rem said
some nice things to me...
Subaru, just calm down for a second.
I'm not sure what you're trying to say,
but I can tell you're trying
your hardest to say it, okay?
So just take it slow, like a good boy.
"Like a good boy"? That's not
exactly encouraging.
But... okay.
I'm just gonna come out and say it, like a man!
The thing is...
Rem said she loves me, the same way
I told you that I love you! So...
Subaru...
Yes?
Who...
is Rem?
You don't look very happy, Rem.
Are you still worried?
Crusch-sama...
Felis and Wilhelm, and all the volunteers
fighting alongside us, are the best of the best.
Ricardo and the Iron Fang are
lending us their aid, too.
Such an assembly cannot lose.
Is it selfish of me to worry despite all that?
It's as Natsuki Subaru said...
You look best when you're smiling.
Honestly...
That Subaru-kun is such a troublemaker.
I'm sure you would also look
quite different with a smile,
since you always carry
yourself with such dignity.
I believe you would look lovely if you smiled.
Yes, well...
I'm not very good at smiling.
It is something I still regret, even now.
Enemy attack!
Run him over!
Crusch-sama!
I wish you wouldn't do that.
Ordering them to run me over
when I'm not doing anything?
That's not something any
decent human being would do.
How dare you do such a brutal
thing to my retainers?
Just who are you?
I see, I see.
You don't know who I am.
But I know who you are.
You're a candidate to be the
next ruler of this nation.
You talk too much.
Answer my question!
Next time, I will kill you!
Now that's just mean.
But I suppose one could never hope to rule
a country without some degree of arrogance.
I can't comprehend that
sensibility myself, but...
I told you there would be no second chances!
Now, look here!
Who taught you that it was acceptable
to swing a sword at someone
when they're happily talking?
I do believe that's a violation
of my right to speak!
Crusch-sama!
Felis...
Ah...
I keep eating and eating,
but it's never enough!
I eat, I devour, I chew, I bite,
I gorge, I gnaw, I munch, I crunch...
Pure gluttony!
Ah, thank you for this feast!
You two are...
Sin Archbishop of the Witch's Cult,
representing gluttony...
Lye Batenkaitos.
And the Sin Archbishop of the
Witch's Cult, representing greed,
Regulus Corneas.
We came here because we heard
our pet had been slain,
and look at this bounty!
I expected them to be a good, ripe bunch,
considering they managed to kill
a beast that had been rampaging
unchecked for 400 years...
But this is beyond my expectations!
Nice! Good! Great! Excellent! Fine!
Perfect! Fantastic! Stupendous!
How long it has been since our
hunger was so thoroughly sated!
You can relax. I'm nothing
like that guy there.
I hate fighting and stuff.
All that "hunger" and "thirst" nonsense?
Such petty self-indulgences are beneath me.
Were you even listening?
Did I not just say that I hate fighting?
Is that all you wish to say,
witch cultist?
Soon enough, a hero will appear
and rid us of all of you.
The one and only hero... whom I love.
Oh? A hero? I look forward to that.
And who are you?
The head maid of the mansion of
Margrave Roswaal L. Mathers...
and currently, the caretaker
of my one and only love,
my beloved Natsuki Subaru,
who will one day be that hero...
Rem!
You'd better be ready, Sin Archbishop!
I promise you, my hero will soon be here
to bring you to justice!
Ah, what mettle!
I am most certainly going to enjoy...
this feast!
Thank you for the feast.
How awful...
What happened here?
Where's Rem?
Where is Rem?!
It's just like before!
Who is Rem?
I have no younger sister.
Rem?
Just like the time when the White Whale got Rem!
But I know we defeated the White Whale!
So why?!
Rem! Where are you?!
If you hear me, say something, Rem!
Rem!
Not her...
Rem! Rem!
Rem!
Rem! Rem! Rem!
Rem...
Where did you go, Rem?
Rem!
Come on, Rem, wake up! It's me!
Hey, Rem?
Rem... Rem!
You know this girl?
Yes! She's Rem!
She's alive, right?! Why won't she wake up?!
Unfortunately, she's beyond help.
Nothing I can do will wake her—
Why?! And you call yourself a healer?!
If you're a healer, then heal her!
Wake her up with magic! Right now!
Come on!
Please...
Come on...
If I Return by Death now...
I'll have to fight Petelgeuse again.
But I don't care.
I'll fight him as many times as it takes...
beat him as many times as it takes...
to save both Emilia and Rem.
I won't let either of them die!
If it'll save both of you...
I'll...
As many times as it takes!
Are you all right?
Subaru, what's the matter?
Where's Rem?
What happened to Rem?
Subaru...
Who...
is Rem?
Now that I think about it,
I never really saw you sleeping before.
You always woke up before me.
Before I realized it,
you were already in my room,
watching me sleep.
Rem...
I'm sorry, Rem.
I tried to sound all brave,
saying I'd die as many times as
it would take to save you...
But I guess no matter how many times I die,
I'll never make it in time.
Oh, it's just you, Puck.
"Just" me? I don't think that was necessary.
You're so mean.
So what brings you all the way out here?
I have a connection with
this girl too, remember?
So what's wrong with me dropping
by to check in on her?
Puck, couldn't you—
Sorry, but not even my power can
wake her from the sleep she's in.
It might not do much to make up for that,
but I could tell you a bit about Gluttony.
Gluttony?
The one who devoured her name and memories.
Put simply, the Authority of Gluttony
is a power for eating.
He can eat someone's name and
make everyone forget about them,
or make that person lose their
own memories by eating them.
If both your name and your memories are taken,
there'll be nothing left
of you but an empty shell.
That's what happened to this girl.
Subaru...
What?!
I hate to ask a favor of you when you've
already got so much on your mind...
But I'm counting on you to take care of Lia.
So this is where you were.
How is she?
No changes at all.
It's not as if there's anything I can even do...
I know I'm weak and pathetic, and yet...
That's not true at all.
I believe you made her quite happy, in fact.
I'm sorry... That was crossing a line.
I've made you upset, haven't I?
No.
Anyway, were you looking for me
because you needed something?
Yes. Everyone has gathered in
the lounge to discuss things.
And, well... um...
It's Natsuki Subaru.
I'm sorry. Of course,
you're Natsuki Subaru-sama.
I've been told that I owe you a great deal,
and yet I've been nothing but rude.
Please forgive me.
Nah, you can't help it.
I know you have a lot to remember right now.
It doesn't bother me, Crusch-san.
Crusch-sama, I'm sorry for making
you deliver that message.
No, it's quite all right, Felis-san.
It's just "Felis."
You and I have known each other for ages.
It makes me sad when you talk
to me like you don't know me.
I'm sorry.
I know it won't be like before,
but I'll try my best, Felis.
There's no need to rush.
I'll always be on your side, Crusch-sama!
Besides, it's like I'm seeing
a whole new side to you now!
Subaru?
It's okay. I've calmed down now, Emilia-tan.
I'm just fine.
Well, now that Subaru-dono and
Crusch-sama have returned,
let us talk.
Let's start by reviewing
where we currently stand.
By the time the Iron Fang
members who got away
brought back reinforcements
from the capital,
the only ones left were the casualties and...
...those in situations similar to mine.
Crusch-san's memories were eaten,
and Rem lost both her name and her memories...
The capital has also had many cases
of memory loss that no healer
could fix, like Crusch-sama,
and an unexplained malady they've
dubbed the "Sleeping Beauty disease."
But now, all of that...
...should be considered the
work of the Witch's Cult.
Oh, I meant nothing against you, Crusch-sama.
I do apologize for frightening you.
No, I apologize for being
such a hopeless master.
I've been trying my hardest to
remember you, as well, but...
We finally took care of Sloth,
and now there's another
Sin Archbishop? This really sucks.
Of course, the moment Emilia-sama became
a candidate in the royal selection,
we knew the Witch's Cult would get involved.
Maybe... it really is my fault.
Well, that's true.
They're fixated on getting rid
of Emilia-sama, the half-elf.
What's going on now is just a tiny part of—
Cut it out! That's ridiculous!
Give a little more thought to what you say!
The only ones at fault here are those scumbags!
Don't put all the blame on the wrong person!
Hurting your own allies with
misdirected blame isn't gonna help!
Hmm? Coming from you, Subaru-kyun,
that's so much more convincing.
I guess it's the difference in experience?
Felis.
I cannot ignore the comment you just made.
Apologize.
Natsuki Subaru-sama is right.
It is crystal clear where
the blame should fall.
Plus, you do not have the
right to ridicule someone
who has made a correct statement.
Yes, Crusch-sama.
Emilia-sama, I apologize.
To you, too, Subaru-kyun.
Forget it. Let's just get back on topic.
But just let me say this.
About the alliance we spoke of...
Can we just scrap that idea?
What do you mean by that?
How did all this lead to the subject
of dissolving the alliance?
An alliance is formed when it
benefits all parties involved.
You expect us to ally ourselves
with Emilia-sama, the Witch Cult's target?
Can you promise that Crusch-sama
won't be hurt again if we do that?
Well...
I am opposed to that opinion.
Why would you be opposed, Old Man Wil?!
Look what's happened to Crusch-sama!
What point is there in continuing to
assist Emilia-sama and her friends?!
With regard to this "Gluttony,"
the one who attacked Crusch-sama...
We may be given an opportunity for revenge.
Is that more important than Crusch-sama's life?!
Felis...
I know this is hard on Crusch-sama, too!
She has no idea what's going on,
she can't remember anything...
So how can you expect her to fight?!
Isn't that right? Isn't it?!
I'm sure I can do something
about your memories!
Even if it's not enough right now,
I'll fix this with my magic!
So please don't put yourself
in any more danger!
Felis, thank you for worrying about me.
Right now, there is simply
too much I don't understand.
I can't remember a single detail
about who I used to be.
I'm sure all of you are perplexed as to
how you should interact with me, too.
But to everyone who still retains their
respect for me despite all this,
I must express my thanks.
Felis, I know that your
concern for me is genuine,
and that you are trying to guide me.
I could do as you say and walk
the path that is safest.
But I loathe the thought of going
on with my life, knowing nothing.
If I have a choice, I would
rather choose for myself
than simply do as someone says.
Crusch-sama...
Felis...
If this is Crusch-sama's will,
surely no one would be in favor
of dissolving the alliance.
Right.
I know I will be a great deal of trouble to
you, Emilia-sama and Natsuki Subaru-sama.
No, it's all right.
We can't exactly say we're all
on the same page, either.
We need to rejoin Ram and everyone
else who's at the Sanctuary,
and we need to talk it over with Roswaal, too.
You said I was strong,
but without you,
I can't even find the Subaru who
could put on that tough guy act, Rem.
I knew you'd be here.
Oh... Emilia.
Did you need something?
Am I not allowed to be here if I don't?
I know this girl... Rem-san, too, don't I?
"Rem-san," huh?
Oh, right...
I just called her "Rem" before.
Well, you're basically Roswaal's guest.
I don't need to explain that
she's Ram's sister, right?
Yes, I can tell.
She looks just like her.
There's no mistaking that.
Subaru, you haven't slept at all, have you?
You should rest for a while.
It's not like I'm doing anything
that'd make me tired.
It's not like I can do anything.
But it's true that you want
to do something, right?
If your spirit keeps trying
so hard for so long,
your body will wear out first.
So... please.
I'm so pathetic.
No, you're not.
You've helped me so much, Subaru.
I really mean it.
It'll all be fine...
Not that I have any right
to talk as if I know that.
I want to understand how you feel,
but since I don't remember
anything about this girl,
I know anything I say will just hurt you.
But...
Just know this, please.
Don't burden yourself with carrying
the weight of Rem alone.
Let me carry your burdens with you.
Emilia...
But you don't even remember
anything about Rem.
Is it wrong to want to do something
if I don't remember her?
She's important enough to you that
it's made you this sad, right?
Is it so strange that it makes
me want to help her, too?
Just like you saved me,
I want to save you this time.
If you're in pain, I want
to do something for you.
You're amazing, Emilia-tan.
Really? I think you're much
more amazing than me.
No, I'm really not.
I'm glad it was you.
Emilia... I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
Could you turn around?
I'm going to cry.
All right.
I swear...
I will get you back.
I swear it.
I'm going to...
Your hero is going to come for you!
I swear it!
Just wait for me,
Each One's Promise
Rem.